[KNOCK ON DOOR]
(Leonard:)-Sheldon, you got a minute?
-Of course, my good friend. Come in.
Yeah, help me out.
(Sheldon:)Which ski hat says,
"Après Super Collider"?
(Scene:)Sheldon,
I'm not taking you to Switzerland.
(Sheldon:)Well, of course you are.
Who else would you take?
(Raj:)-Penny.
-What? That's absurd.
(Sheldon:)Penny has no interest
in subatomic particle research.
(Leonard:)Yes, but it'll be Valentine's Day.
(Leonard:)We can go sightseeing and skiing
and make love in front of a roaring fire...
(Leonard:)...in the shadow
of the snow-capped Alps.
(Sheldon:)But Penny has no interest
in subatomic particle research.
(Leonard:)I'm sorry, Sheldon.
(Sheldon:)Sorry? I've been dreaming about
going to the Large Hadron Collider...
...since I was 9 years old.
(Leonard:)I've been dreaming about spending
Valentine's with a girl since I was 6.
(Sheldon:)Shame on you.